Okay, I'm sorry to bother you, but your father and I just had a huge fight.
That man.
Anyway, you know how your dad is.
I'm really sorry to bother you.
I can't sleep in there with him right now.
It's just, it's too much.
Your brother moved out.
I know you have an extra bunk.
I promise I won't bother you.
I just need to sleep in here tonight.
Is that okay?
Alright.
Okay.
Thanks.
Now, I need to get some sleep.
I have a big day tomorrow.
doing go to sleep oh my god are you doing what I think you're doing okay you need to sleep because I need to sleep all right like I know you're a horny young man but this is not the time it's highly inappropriate
Oh my god.
Alright, look.
Look, I know I'm just your stepmom, but I need you to behave yourself right now.
This is so inappropriate, alright?
Okay, look, I know what it's like to be your age.
I know you're just going to jerk off.
I can't believe I'm saying this.
I will help you if you will just go to sleep.
How's that sound?
Deal?
You can't tell your father, though.
Do you understand?
All right.
So you want to jerk off?
Then show me how you jerk off.
Pull it out.
That's what I thought.
You have a pretty big cock, actually, don't you?
Alright.
Stroke it.
Okay, I know you were stroking it harder than that.
I could hear you.
Do it the way you usually do it.
Show me.
Okay, you want me to do it for you?
Alright.
Fine.
You like that, don't you?
Just a horny young man.
I have to say, it's kind of hot.
It's been a while since I've been with such a young man.
And your father's so old.
I could be such a grump about everything.
You want to see my tits?
Is that what you want to see?
All right.
I'm going to help you.
There you go.
I can feel you getting harder on my hand, can't you?
Like the way I'm stroking it?
You like it more on the tip?
Or you like it when I do the whole shaft like this?
You like the tip, don't you?
That's right.
I can feel you getting harder.
Hey, no touching.
You can look, but you can't touch.
Understand?
I don't think you need to touch anyway, do you?
Oh, there you go.
Just like that.
I can feel you getting nice and hard.
You want to help me stroke it?
Help me.
I want to see how you do it.
I'm just going to rub the tip and take the whole shaft.
Oh, I work the balls.
You like that, don't you?
Just like that, I wanna see you do it.
I wanna see you do it.
I see these tits, look at my tits.
Look at my tits while I do this.
While I rub your balls.
That's right.
You're such a bad boy.
But you've always been my favorite.
Just don't tell your brother or your father.
I've always thought you were a very handsome young man.
I can tell the way you've been looking at my tits that you think I'm kind of hot too, don't you?
Well, for a woman my age, that's a compliment.
Oh, I know you like it.
But you can't get a handjob like this from the girls at your school, could you?
There's something to be said for age and experience.
At least I can pass it along to you, huh?
Oh, I know you like that.
I'm gonna make you come, aren't I?
That's right.
Just like that.
I want you to come all over my hand.
Come all over my hand.
Not yet.
I want you to be a little bit harder and a little bit more turned on.
And I'll tell you when to come.
How about that?
Help me stroke it.
It's getting me pretty hot too.
Oh yeah.
Just like that.
You gonna come now?
I want you to come now.
Wow.
Alright.
Now.
Be a good boy.
Go to sleep.